Name: Jezz Lucena Phone: (774) 232-8373 Email: jezzlucena@gmail.com	
Portfolio: https://jezzlucena.com	
##### Summary #####	
I'm passionate about crafting magical user experiences and constantly explore the latest technologies and trend Bachelor's in Computer Engineering and a Master's in Interactive Media & Game Development, my ongoing education ability to deliver exceptional results in both full-time and contract roles.	
##### Technical Skills #####	
Coding Languages & Frameworks: JavaScript, TypeScript, React.js, Redux, Next.js, Node.js, Python, Django, Phoen. PHP, HTML 5, CSS 3 Tongues: English, Portuguese, Spanish Other: jQuery, Agile, SASS, LESS, Git, UX/UI Design	ix, Elixir,
##### Professional Experience #####	
AES, San Mateo,CA Full Stack Engineer • Established a robust deployment pipeline across development, staging, and production environments, streamlin with technologies such as PHP, HTML5, CSS3, ES6, and Git. • Spearheaded the development of a WordPress-based student/teacher platform, enhancing the educational web app and increasing student retention rates by 20%.	
	2021 - 01/2023
UI EngineerLed the rebranding of Zazzle Plus, integrating React, TypeScript, C#, and SQL Server to deliver scalable dis	tributed
features.Drove significant growth through strategic A/B testing, achieving a 15% increase in user engagement or subscof the premium service.	ription rates
MakersPlace, San Francisco, CA Full Stack Engineer	2020 - 05/2021
 Managed Full Stack development for a digital art gallery using Python, JavaScript (ES6), and jQuery. Gained firsthand experience with Ethereum blockchain, contributing to 100% growth in peak transaction volume 	
Law Office of Robert B Jobe, San Francisco, CA Lead Software Engineer 01/	2019 - 12/2019
• Developed a comprehensive case management, HR, and billing solution, improving operational efficiency by red delinquency by 30% and case processing time by 15%.	lucing payment
##### Education #####	
Worcester Polytechnic Institute (WPI) - Worcester, MA MSc, Interactive Media and Game Development	2018
Universidade Federal do Rio Grande do Norte - Natal, Brazil BEng, Computer Engineering	2015